<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Divisions of Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="division1">Barisal District, officially known as Barishal District is a district in south-central Bangladesh, formerly called Bakerganj district, established in 1797.Its headquarters are in the city of Barisal,
which is also the headquarters of Barisal Division.</string>
    <string name="division2">Chittagong Division is geographically the largest of the eight administrative divisions of Bangladesh. It covers the south-easternmost areas of the country, with a total area of and a population at the 2011 census of 28,423,019. The administrative division includes mainland Chittagong District, neighbouring districts and the Chittagong Hill Tracts.Chittagong Division is ho.</string>

    <string name="division3">Dhaka Division is an administrative division within Bangladesh.Dhaka is the capital city of Bangladesh and also the largest city as well of the country. It comes among the 10 most populous cities of the world. The Division as constituted prior to 2015 covered an area of 31,051 km2,and had a population of 47,424,418 at the 2011 Census. However, following the separation of th.</string>

    <string name="division4">The Khulna division borders the North 24 Parganas district and South 24 Parganas district of West Bengal to the west,
 the Rajshahi Division to the north, the Dhaka division and the Barisal division to the east, and has a coastline on
the Bay of Bengal to the south. It is part of the Ganges River delta or Greater Bengal Delta. Other rivers include
the Madhumati River, the Bhairab River and the Kopotokkho River. The region also includes several islands in the Bay
of Bengal.</string>

    <string name="division5">Mymensingh is the capital of Mymensingh Division of Bangladesh. The city is located on </string>

    <string name="division6">Rajshahi is a metropolitan city, and a major urban, commercial and educational centre of Bangladesh.
It is also the administrative seat of eponymous division and district. Located on the north bank of the Padma River,
near the Bangladesh-India border, the city has a population of over 763,952 residents</string>
    <string name="division7">Rangpur is a metropolitan city, and a major urban, commercial and educational centre of Bangladesh.
It is also the administrative seat of eponymous division and district. Located on the north bank of the Padma River,
near the Bangladesh-India border, the city has a population of over 763,952 residents</string>
    <string name="division8">Sylhet is a metropolitan city, and a major urban, commercial and educational centre of Bangladesh.
It is also the administrative seat of eponymous division and district. Located on the north bank of the Padma River,
near the Bangladesh-India border, the city has a population of over 763,952 residents</string>



</resources>